<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kencho51</title>
    <link>https://kencho51.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on kencho51</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>kencho51</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:13:43 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kencho51.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OOP</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:13:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</guid>
      <description>What is OOP? Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes. This helps keep code following the tenet &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t repeat yourself&amp;rdquo; (DRY) and easy-to-maintain.
 Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes.
 What is a class?  A blueprint for a house. It defines the shape of the house on paper, with relationships between the different parts of the house clearly defined and planned out, even though the house doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, Todo and Done 25-29/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/25-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 11:22:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/25-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Using Yii to build a blog system PHP  To-do  Yii tutorial To practice PHP  Done  Yii 2 crash course OOP:Don&#39;t Repeat Yourself and easy to maintain
2.1 Encapsulation
2.2 Abstraction
2.3 Inheritance
2.4 Polymorphism  Resources  Yii Best Yii Best Free Yii2 Tutorials OOP concepts OOP code examples  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to format text using Markdown?</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/markdownsyntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:39:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/markdownsyntax/</guid>
      <description>Markdown is a simple way to format text that looks great on any device. It doesn’t do anything fancy like change the font size, color, or type — just the essentials, using keyboard symbols you already know. Here is the source of the following cheatsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP progress</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/phpprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 17:48:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/phpprogress/</guid>
      <description>Learning PHP at Codecademy Topics   String and variables - Done
  Number - Done
  Functions - Done
  Intro to Built-in PHP functions - Done
 find variable types
gettype(); var_dump(); string functions
strrev();strtolower(); strtoupper(); str_repeat(); substring
substr_count(); number function
abs(); round(); generating random numbers
rand(); getrandmax(); ceil(); documentation
str_pad(); check value in array
in_array(&amp;quot;valuetocheck&amp;quot;, $array)    Ordered Arrays
 can be integer or string or any data type $my_array = array(); or $my_array=[]; returns the array length</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github usage example</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/githubusageexample/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:55:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/githubusageexample/</guid>
      <description>The development cycle of the gigadb. 1. fork gigadb-website 2. clone the gigadb-website into local SSD git clone https://github.com/kencho51/gigadb-website.git
3. add remote origin git remote add origin https://github.com/kencho51/gigadb-website.git
4. add remote upstream origin git remote add upstream https://github.com/gigascience/gigadb-website.git
5. follow here to build the docker container for the testing. 6. The flow to make changes: 6.1 Create branch for an issue git branch issue-no
6.2 Go to that branch
git checkout issue-no</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 18-22/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/18-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:00:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/18-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  php Yii  To-do  Study github issues.  start issue#160  url for Editorial board url for github update the content     Start PHP Numbers at Codecademy. Start Yii, learn how to build a blog system.  Done  Personal hugo page released. Finined PHP course at Codecademy. Made pull request for issue 160  Resources  For Yii, link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo page is released</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/deployhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 12:24:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/deployhugo/</guid>
      <description>A personal website for Gigathing is settup and deployed. Here is the link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a hugo website</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/howtomakeahugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/howtomakeahugo/</guid>
      <description>Aim Try to build a hugo website to log everything happened in GigaScience.
Description The website will contain:
 About Contact Posts  To-do Done Learning progress   Projects  How Comming soon&amp;hellip;
How to make a public folder In config.toml, add this: publishDir = &amp;quot;public&amp;quot;
link
Add Google Analytics feature How to set up a Google Analytics, steps followed here.
How to add a disqus Follow here
sources:  freecodecamp medium medium RStudio  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test update new post to public</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/test/</guid>
      <description>Useful materials  sources  freecodecamp medium    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have done</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/14-05-2020_done/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/14-05-2020_done/</guid>
      <description>Issue #198 Found out that the commited changes cannot be seen in the local gigadb.
 rollbacked to commit ID: 3954c0b0, and make two changes in help.html.dist and help.php. still cannot see the changes in local gigadb website.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Every day is a new day, keep up and never give up!
School 2017 MSc in Genomics and Bioinformatics The University of Hong Kong
2014 BSc in Biotechnology The University of Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Email: kencho.gigascience@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have learned</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/13-05-2020-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/13-05-2020-log/</guid>
      <description>Learning  learn PHP in codecademy try to start Yii  Hands on  keep fixing #374  Some keypoints 1.concatenation assigment $fruits = &amp;ldquo;apple&amp;rdquo;;
$fruits .= &amp;quot; orange&amp;rdquo;;
echo $fruits; //will return &amp;lsquo;apple orange&amp;rsquo;
2.assign by reference $order = &amp;ldquo;5 eggs&amp;rdquo;;
$new-order =&amp;amp; $order;
$new-order .=&amp;rdquo;, 8 hams&amp;rsquo;;
echo $order; // will return &amp;lsquo;5 eggs, 8 hams&amp;rsquo;
echo $new-order; // will return &amp;lsquo;5 eggs, 8 hams&amp;rsquo;
3.curly brackets $name = &amp;ldquo;Ken&amp;rdquo;;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My awesome project</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/reference/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>